Shefali Natha

+91 9545819758 · shefalinatha@gmail.com

Summary

Highly analytical and process oriented data analyst with in-depth knowledge of analytical tools, research methodologies, big data capture, curation, manipulation and analysing. Furnish insights, analytics and business intelligence used to advance opportunity identification and drive successful business solutions. Thoroughly motivated individual who works well with minimum supervision in a challenging, fast paced and deadline-oriented environment. Expertise Includes:

SQL
Python
Dashboarding(Tableau,Google Sheet)
Automation

Team Management
Data Analysis
Problem Solving
Continuous Process Improvement

Experience

Uber Senior Business Analyst,ART Hyderabad, India July 2019-Currently working

Marketing Analytics

- Handled global marketing (Post Analysis Campaigns) for both eats and rides across various regions (APAC,EMEA, US&CANADA etc).
- Helped in creating google sheet Dashboards for tracking signup funnel, churn and resurrection rate for eats and rides.
- Automated the weekly/monthly refresh of above dashboards with the help of python scripts.
- Build the acquisition and performance related on dashboards on dashbuilder v1.0

Global Quality

- Worked on Global Quality Scorecard Dashboard thus helping in Quality metrics like (AHT,CSAT etc)
- Automated both the dashboards using python script since the data in sheet was captured from different data sources.
- Worked extensively on SQL Queries , helped different teams by sharing insightful analysis which created an impact.
- Automated the Queue loading process for the Global Quality Team.
- Created temporary tables using uworc(uber tool) to optimise the query run for sampling process.

ZS AssociatesBusiness Technology Analyst

Pune, India March 2017 – August 2018

AZ Alignment & Targeting

- Worked on Javelin Alignment Manager Software an integrated tool of ZS.
- Responsible for handling and analysing the data related to geography restructuring (Alignment) and Targeting.
- Creating summaries and Dashboards with all the monthly changes.
- Automating the summary creation process using informatica workflow thus reducing manual hour from 48 hours to 1 hour.
- Presenting monthly summaries to stakeholders and clients.

Project Alpha

- Helped in restructuring all the teams of AZ to enable the client to reduce the number of Rep count working for them.
- Responsible for post analyses of the headcount in territories and reporting through excel dashboards.

Yardi SoftwaresSoftware Engineer

Pune, India July 2016 – February 2017

- Yardi Software is a leading provider of high-performance software solutions for the real estate industry.
- Performed extensive data analysis and produced reports and project status to senior management and business partners on data discrepancies.
- Designed solutions by actively engaging with clients for troubleshooting the issues.
- Demonstrated MOM data to clients using Excel dashboards.

Education

MPSTME NMIMS, Mumbai,MH B.Tech – Computer Engineering (CGPA 3.67/4) 2012-2016 IIS, Jaipur, Rajasthan, IN XII CBSE Board (90.1%) 2012
Warren Academy School,
Jaipur, Rajasthan, IN
X RBSE Board
(92.7%)
2010

Additional

- Gold Medalist for 2012-2016 in NMIMS.
- Ehsaas Volunteer for "Donate your goods(clothes, stationary)" program (2014, 2015)
- Awarded **Gargi** prize by Rajasthan government for securing 92.17% in Board examination (2010)
- Golden ticket receiver for outstanding performance in Q4 2019.
- Awarded as all rounder in school.
- Headed and supported various college committees like ISTE(Finance and PR), Flavium(Cultural).